hi I'm feeling pretty low this morning I
drop my kid off for her first full day
of grade two and this was so much harder
than dropping her off for kindergarten
because the school I thought she was
going to go through go to from K through
to grade 12 got closed at the end of
last year and so now she's in a regular
public school and although I'm sure it
is amazing in and of itself it isn't the
one that we left it isn't the community
it isn't the kids it isn't the teachers
and sitting here with that feeling and
then I posted it on our Facebook group
from the school old school and there was
a pouring of love which somehow makes
you feel better I mean makes me feel
better and worse because it's like yep
that's the community and also the
community and so I was listening to
music to try to get myself in a more
positive space to do these this video I
can't say it succeeded and part of what
I got what the video I was going to do
today I've written on my whiteboard here
that you don't need to be it we will be
it and by it I literally mean all the
things that society dictates for
supposed to be if you're rich smart
connected strong brave fast powerful as
individuals you don't need to be any or
all of those things because collectively
we will be those things and that is the
world we are creating together with the
tech cooperative with the disability and
yet I just drop my kid off at a school
that teaches her as almost all public
schools do that you have to be
everything you have to be smart in
science and math and language and
spelling or your less than and I know
that's not the language they are going
to use and that's not the message she's
gonna get at home she's gonna
consistently get the you are perfect
exactly as you are and so is everybody
else do what you love and who cares what
you're good about a there is a space for
you well I am actively creating that
world that makes that true
through the power of technology we can
share in each other's strength and
bravery and intelligence and compassion
and power and speed and then coming home
and trying to do that and also feeling
inadequate I've continually need this
message I am exactly who I meant to be
yes I don't know how to code I can't do
the executive functioning required to
get this project off the ground
I can't edit the video and sometimes I
do sit in that space and feel like
and that is not the truth the truth is
I'm exactly who I meant to be the right
people are coming I am getting the right
next step next step next step to get
this thing going even if I keep
continually feeling like I'm isolated
alone because I also know that I'm not I
know when I reach out I'm connect I'm
surrounded by amazing compassionate
intelligent people that want this planet
to be better and want to do better
themselves and as a group even if they
don't see the vision that I keep putting
out in the world
the visions gonna get there it's going
to get to the right people and together
we will create the vision it gets to
everyone because a better world is on
its way and it's going to be brought to
you by everybody everybody working
together give me the pieces that they
are amazing at being seen and still
loved as worthy for the pieces the
society says is lacking they're not
lacking you're exactly who you're
supposed to be I'm exactly who I'm
supposed to be and together we are going
to create a better world with our
physical emotional emotional and mental
diversity
and I posted on reddit I just found
through the discord which I had a whole
other rant for I don't like discord I
don't like slack I don't like any of the
new technologies that are out there
because they're not designed for people
who suck at technology they're not
designed to be intuitive and they're
confusing and don't work for my brain
but I'm on it I'm on discord because
there's a cooperative community and I
love cooperative community there but on
there they posted that there's a
subreddit that's cooperatives I was like
what's cool awesome so I posted on there
and I will post that in the links
explaining a bit of what it is I'm
trying to do to find people find the
people to make the Bata world cafe hope
cafe platform that helps us have a real
world conversation and to just get
together weekly to discuss cooperative
and disability League and move forward
on creating the actual system that helps
bring people on board easily because if
it's this hard for everyone you guys
aren't going to do it and nor should you
but the beauty is it's not because we
don't have to be everything we get to
each be who we powerfully intellectually
all those words are and together we are
so much better I've said this a few
times so good closing it a few times but
a better world is on its way it's gonna
be brought to you by the physically and
neurodiverse please like like and
subscribe I will see you tomorrow
take care